$Acrobat	Acrobat
$AcrobatDesc	The kind of person that uses agility and endurance to their advantage. Unafraid of jumping long distances.
$Agent	Agent
$AgentDesc	Charming when they can be seen, and nearly invisible when in shadow.
$Archer	Archer
$ArcherDesc	A marksman, adept at combat at great distances. Able to take down most foes before they have a chance to draw sword.
$Assassin	Assassin
$AssassinDesc	Nimble and quiet, they move in darkness to strike at the unsuspecting. Locks hold no doors shut for them.
$Barbarian	Barbarian
$BarbarianDesc	Fearsome brutes who inspire fear and dread in the hearts of their enemies. Like a storm, swift and powerful. Finding little use for heavy armor, they rely on smashing their foes into the ground.
$Bard	Bard
$BardDesc	Intelligent and personable, they prefer to accomplish tasks with their words first, and sword second.
$Battlemage	Battlemage
$BattlemageDesc	Able to resolve most conflicts with either spell or sword. They are a deadly mix of scholar and soldier.
$Crusader	Crusader
$CrusaderDesc	A combatant who wields the power of brute strength and medicinal knowledge. Cheating death after every fight, they rely on their keen knowledge of restoration to fight yet again.
$Healer	Healer
$HealerDesc	Fighters of poison and illness. The ancient art of restoration is their ally, and the deadly art of destruction is their weapon.
$Knight	Knight
$KnightDesc	The most noble of all combatants. Strong in body and in character.
$Mage	Mage
$MageDesc	Prefering to use their extensive knowledge of all things magical, they wield a might more powerful than the sharpest blade.
$Monk	Monk
$MonkDesc	Quick and cunning with the empty hand, they are strong in spirit. They prefer to solve conflict by arrow or by fist.
$Nightblade	Nightblade
$NightbladeDesc	Spell and shadow are their friends. By darkness they move with haste, casting magic to benefit their circumstances.
$Pilgrim	Pilgrim
$PilgrimDesc	Hearty folk, well-versed in the tomes of old. They profit in life by bartering in the market, or by persuading the weak-minded.
$Rogue	Rogue
$RogueDesc	They use speed in combat rather than brute force. Persuasive in conversation, their tongues are as sharp as blades.
$Scout	Scout
$ScoutDesc	Preferring the rolling countryside to the city life, they are gifted with the ability to evade, guard, and protect themselves with great proficiency.
$Sorcerer	Sorcerer
$SorcererDesc	Besting the most well-equipped fighters, they rely on the spells of the mystic arts. Unique to these mages is the bodily stamina to be armed with the thickest armor.
$Spellsword	Spellsword
$SpellswordDesc	More nimble and athletic than the sorcerer, and better suited for spell-casting than the knight, their attacks are unpredictable. Students of combat and magic.
$Thief	Thief
$ThiefDesc	Profiting from the losses of others is their love. Able to be swift in shadow, and crafty in bartering. Locks are enemies, and lock-picks are their swords.
$Outlander	Outlander
$OutlanderDesc	The wilds are in their blood, whether they were a nomad, an explorer, a recluse, a hunter-gatherer, or even a marauder.
$Warrior	Warrior
$WarriorDesc	Unafraid of light weaponry, they plow into the fray with little regard for injury. Masters of all melee tools, they put little faith in the magical arts.
$Witchhunter	Witchhunter
$WitchhunterDesc	Swift on foot, and clever with spells, they use distance as their ally. Slower adversaries are fodder for their arrows.
$FocusCombat	Combat
$FocusMagic	Magic
$FocusStealth	Stealth
$SpecFocus	Specialization
$SpecAttribs	Attributes
$AttrStrength	Strength
$AttrIntelligence	Intelligence
$AttrWillpower	Willpower
$AttrAgility	Agility
$AttrSpeed	Speed
$AttrEndurance	Endurance
$AttrPersonality	Personality
$AttrLuck	Luck
$AttrFaith	Faith
$MajorSkills	Major Skills
$specCustom	Custom Class
$sdsClass	Class
$equipLoad	Equip Load
$sdsClassMenuSelect	Create your character
$sdsClassMenuTitle	Class Selection
$skOne	One-Handed
$skTwo	Two-Handed
$skArch	Marksman
$skBlock	Block
$skSmith	Smithing
$skHeavy	Heavy armor
$skLight	Light armor
$skPick	Pickpocketing
$skLock	Lockpicking
$skSneak	Sneak
$skAlch	Alchemy
$skSpeech	Speechcraft
$skAlter	Alteration
$skConj	Conjuration
$skDestr	Destruction
$skIll	Illusion
$skRes	Restoration
$skEnch	Enchanting
$sdsSkills	Skills
$sdsConfirm	Confirm
$sdsSkillPoints	Skill Points
$sdsLevelUpMenu	Level Up
$sdsInventoryMenu	Inventory
$sdsMagic	Magic
$sdsSystem	System
$sdsMap	Map
$cardBasePowers	Base Power
$cardDefense	Defense
$cardResistances	Resistances
$DefMagicRes	Magic
$DefDiseaseRes	Disease
$DefFireRes	Fire
$DefFrostRes	Frost
$DefShockRes	Shock
$DefPoisonRes	Poison
$BaseCarryInfo	Carry Weight
$BaseStaminaRate	Stamina Rate
$BaseMagickaRate	Magicka Rate
$BaseSpellMastery	Spell Mastery
$SDSConfirmLevelUp	Are you sure?
$SDSLevelupTooltip	Choose skills and attributes to levelup
$FinalizeCreation	Finalize creation
$EntryIncomplete	Entry Incomplete
$Appearance	Appearance
$sdsCreateCharacter	Create Character
$EnterName	Enter name
$SelectClass	Select class
$ChooseRace	Choose race
$SelectGender	Select gender
$ChangeAppearance	Change appearance
$ChangeCamera	Camera position
$LoadPreset	Load Character Preset
$SwitchCategory	Switch Category
$SwitchTab	Switch Tab
$RMC_ShowHistory	History
$RMC_HideHistory	Brushes
$sdsClose	Close
$Required	Required
$Preview	Preview
$UILIB_1_CustomHelp	Неблокируемая атака: атака, которую нельзя заблокировать никаким доступным методом, будь то обычный блок или тайминговый блок. От данной атаки можно только увернуться или провести парирование. Неблокируемая атака всегда сопровождается характерным звуком и символом над головой противника
$UILIB_2_CustomHelp	Уворот: с оружием в руках совершите нажатие на кнопку спринта (L ALT) в движении что бы совершить уворот от атаки противника. В самом начале уворота на короткое время вы избегаете любого урона, что позволяет вам увернуться от самых широких ударов, стрел и болтов, а так же от магических атак.
$UILIB_3_CustomHelp	Блокирование: нажмите Правую кнопку мыши что бы заблокировать вражеский удар. Блокирование сводит на нет весь физический урон до тех пор пока у вас есть запас сил. Для блокирования зачарованного оружия разблокируйте тайминговый блок в древе навыков блока. Вы так же можете получить навык парирования, что бы оглушить противника на большой промежуток времени.
$UILIB_4_CustomHelp	Туманная стена: за стеной тумана вас зачастую будет ждать очень сильный противник. Войдя на арену за стеной, вы не сможете покинуть ее до тех пор, пока не убьете вашего соперника.
$UILIB_5_CustomHelp	Забытый храм: Место, куда вы можете всегда вернуться с помощью способности "Возвращение в Храм", что бы отдохнуть, восполнить запасы, или что то приобрести у торговца (Ассортимент увеличивается от перков красноречия). Что бы вернуться в Скайрим используйте клинок возле Стены Алдуина (Телепортирует только в то место где вы уже были)
$Redo	Redo
$Close	Close
$sTravel	Travel
$sLeave	Leave
$sRecharge	Recharge Weapons
$sPassTime	Pass Time
$sCook	Cook
$sdsBonfireTravel	Travel
$SDSTravelMenuTooltip	Select bonfire to travel to.
$sdsEmoteUse	Select gesture to use
$sdsTestEmote	Test now
$sdsSwitchEmote	Switch
$sdsTrainerFocus	Focus
$TrainFocus	Learn